本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版
盖比  你说实话
Gabe, be totally honest.
对于一个孕妇来说
For a pregnant woman,
我是不是很销魂
I'm really smoking, aren't I?
算了  我还是保持沉默吧
Yeah. I think silence is my best option here.
好吧  我去练瑜伽了
Okay. Well, I'm off to yoga.
噢  嘿  在您走之前
Oh hey, before you go...
又是这破玩意
This silly old thing.
您能在这上面随便签个字吗  学校的事
Can I get a quick signature for this thing for school?
学校的事  噢
A school thing? Oh.
希望这次不是校长发来的
I Hope this isn't another note from your principal.
噢  看看啊  有点意思
Oh, look at that. Yes, that's interesting.
“亲爱的邓肯夫人”如今都是印章印的啊
It's gotten to the point where "dear Mrs. duncan" is a stamp.
你往图书馆里扔了一麻袋的蟋蟀
You released a bag of crickets in the library?
-为什么  -蟋蟀吵闹
-Why? -Crickets are noisy.
图书馆安静
The library is quiet.
何乐而不为
You try things.
我想想  我乐而为之的事情有禁足你
Let's see. I could try things like grounding you,
-扣零用钱  -哇  妈
-Cutting your allowance... -Wow, mom,
我现在又仔细地看了看你
Now that I'm getting a better look at you,
你绝对销魂
You are smoking.
-真的吗  -真的
-You really think so? -Yeah.
别拍马屁了  先生  这回你玩大了
Forget it, mister. You've gone too far this time.
我和你爸一会再商量下怎么处罚你
Your father and I will discuss your punishment later.
好吧  好吧
All right, fine,
但你还要把这个签了
But you still have to sign this.
真希望我也有个印章
Wish I had a stamp.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录 www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>Has anybody seen my left shoe</i>
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
■
翻译： Johnny-Z
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof</i>
■
校对： line
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice</i>
■
后期： Johnny-Z  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Your life is up and down</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me it comes back around</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love</i> <i>who you turn out to be</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第二集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E02  Bad Luck Teddy
真高兴咱俩复合了
I'm so glad we're back together.
是啊  我也是
I know. Me too.
我跟你说  我感觉当咱俩幸福的时候
You know, I feel like when we're happy,
-花儿都对咱们笑  -是啊
-The whole world is happy. -Right.
-非也  -噢  嘿
-Guess again. -Oh hey!
你说把咱俩的名字合到一起
Wouldn't it be fun cute couple nicknamese.
变成组合名  会不会很有趣啊
Where we combine our two names?
-比如布拉吉丽娜  -对  对  对
-Like brangelina. -Yeah yeah yeah.
好了  那么
Right, okay. So...
斯宾塞和泰迪
Spencer and Teddy.
噢  可以是“斯宾迪”  你喜欢斯宾迪吗
Oh, we could be "spendy"! Do you like spendy?
我喜欢让斯宾迪给俺一闷棍
I'd like for spendy to hit me over the head with a club.
好了  我该走了
Well, I gotta go...
-去练篮球了  -好的
-Basketball practice. -All right.
再见  斯宾迪
See ya later, spendy.
我喜欢这名字
I like it.
艾薇  为什么大家都用鄙视的眼神看着我
Ivy, why are people giving me dirty looks?
嗯  有很多可能性
Hmm, it could be anything really...
你的裤子啊  你的衣服啊
Your pants, your shirt,
你是个扫把星啊  你的头发
The fact that you're a jinx, your hair.
等等  呜  呜  好了  往回倒一下
Wait. Whoa whoa. Okay, go... go back.
扫把星  这个名字从何而来
I'm a jinx? Why would people think that?
这个嘛  自从你和斯宾塞复合之后
Well, ever since you and spencer got back together,
篮球队就没赢过球
The basketball team hasn't won a game.
太荒唐了  艾薇  不会吧
But that's ridiculous. Ivy, come on.
-你不会也认为我是个扫把星吧  -虽然我不认为
-You don't think I am a jinx, don't you？ -Well I, don't,
但是篮球队这么认为
But the basketball team does,
教练这么认为  还有看门老大爷
The coach does, the janitor... rse,
我不是扫把星
I am not a jinx!
如果非是什么星的话  也是幸运星
If anything, I'm <i>good</i> luck.
抱歉
Sorry.
嘿  看起来不错啊  查莉
Hey, looking good, Charlie.
我知道  爸爸
I know, daddy.
是啊  不愧是你妈的女儿  真像
Yeah, you are your mother's daughter, all right.
噢  下个是我  我要坐那辆跑车
Oh, I'm next! I'll take the race car.
嘿  PJ  PJ
Hey, P.J., P.J.
经理让我找你谈谈
Manager asked me to talk to you.
-谈什么  -过来
-About what? -Come here.
他觉得你坐那辆跑车  年龄有点大了
He seems to think you're a little old to sit in the race car.
好吧  那我去坐大象
All right. I'll sit on the elephant,
但是我发出的引擎声就英雄无用武之地了
But my engine noises won't make any sense.
嘿
Hey.
你都到了可以选举的年龄了
You're old enough to vote.
你也到了可以去成人理发店的年龄了
You're old enough to go to a real barbershop.
但是成人理发店不送贴画和棒棒糖
But real barbershops don't give out stickers and lollipops.
也许你可以将选举权推迟一段时间
Maybe you can hold off on the voting for a little while.
嘿  不如这样  我带你去我平常理发的地方
Hey, you know what? I'll take you to where I get my hair cut.
呃  不了  谢谢
Uh, no thanks.
你十八了
You're 18.
是时候离该开橙色气球  然后成熟起来了
Time to leave the orange balloon and grow up.
噢  你狠  往我的伤口上撒盐
Oh, great, rub it in my face.
你能相信盖比做了什么吗
Can you believe what Gabe did?
不  我不能
No, I can't.
我的意思是  大家都能知道你在捣腾蟋蟀
I mean, everybody knows when you transport crickets.
你不能用麻袋装  你应该用通风箱啊
You don't use a bag, you use a lightly-ventilated box.
扯远了  老鲍  我们要惩罚他
Focus! Bob, we have to punish him.
天啊  他最近又捅了不少篓子
Man, he's been a handful lately.
是啊
I know.
不过  至少咱们还没有惨到和我的朋友帕姆一样
Well, at least we don't have it as bad as my friend Pam.
她是和我一起上瑜伽课的孕妇
She's one of the pregnant gals in my yoga class.
她有个和盖比一样大的儿子  巨淘气
She has a son Gabe's age who's so out of control.
他们就把他送到军事学校了
They're sending him to military school.
军事学校
<i>Military school?</i>
没办法啊  老鲍  你不能让一个
It's the only way, Bob. You can't have.
像他一样的捣蛋鬼在我肚子里的小宝宝周围晃悠
A troublemaker like him around with a new baby on the way.
尽管这样  我是说
Still, I mean,
对一个和盖比差不多大的孩子来说  是不是有点严厉了
Isn't that kinda harsh for a kid Gabe's age?
他缺乏的就是严格管教
What he needs is discipline,
这正是像格雷斯顿学院这样的学校能提供的
And that's what a school like Graystone academy can give him.
是啊  差不多吧  嘿  他知道这件事了吗
Yeah, I guess. Hey, does he know it's happening?
不知道  诀窍就在于不让他知道
No, the trick is <i>not</i> to tell him.
某天你说“嘿  儿子  上车
Then one day you say, "hey, buddy, get in the car.
我们去买冰淇淋”  然后直奔军事学校
We're going for ice cream. " Then off you go to military school.
-哇  我不知道  -就这么定了  老鲍
-Wow. I don't know if I... -It's done, Bob.
你还瞎操心什么  又不是把他送走了
And what do you care? It's not like him leaving.
就会影响到你的生活
Is gonna affect your life one way or the other.
是啊  这倒是
Yeah, that's true.
打扰一下  问个事
Excuse me, quick question:
在你这里理发送什么东西吗
Do you give out prizes with your haircuts?
送  如果我给你弄流血了  我送你卷绷带
Yeah, if I Nick you, you get a free bandage.
您跟我开玩笑呢吧
That's a joke, right?
算是吧
Okay.
哇  看来我真应该少喝点咖啡
Wow, I've really got to cut down on the coffee.
跟您说吧
You know,
我其实想把头发留长一点
I'm actually thinking about letting it grow out anyways.
-雪梨  -嗨
-Syd! -Hi.
-嘿  -坐下吧
-Hey. -Have a seat.
好吧  既然我都来了
Well, since I'm here.
-你怎么称呼  -我叫PJ
-What's your name? -I'm P.J.
今天想剪个什么发型
So what kind of cut would you like today?
呃  这个嘛
Uh, well,
通常我剪英俊王子发型
Normally I go for the handsome prince,
但是今天我想尝试下地痞流氓发型
But today I'm thinking about changing to the sporty rascal.
听着  PJ  我觉着你应该换一种比较成熟的发型
Well, P.J., I think it's time we gave you more of an adult look.
不如来剪个
How about we go...
两边短
Shorter on the sides.
上面长的发型
And then we can layer it on top?
好吧
Okay.
或者剪个上面短
Or we could go shorter on top.
后面长的发型
And then leave it fuller in the back.
哪个花费的时间长  剪哪个
Whatever takes the longest.
来吧  我来给你洗头
Come on, let's get you shampooed.
我要洗头去了
We're gonna get me shampooed.
好了  我要你说实话
Okay, don't sugarcoat it.
大家都认为我是扫把星吗
Does <i>everyone</i> think that I'm a jinx?
是的
Yes.
乖乖  还真是实话实说
Boy, no sugar there.
泰迪  真的很抱歉  只是那些
Teddy, I'm sorry, all right? It's one of those,
-你也知道  体育上的迷信  -但是感觉好傻啊
-You know, sports superstition things. -But it's so stupid.
是啊  我也这么觉着  但是每个人都迷信
Yeah, I know, but everyone believes it.
那好吧  我们就让他们信服我不是扫把星
Well, then we'll just have to convince them that I'm not a jinx.
-怎么做  -你把比赛打好点
-How do we do that? -You could play better.
我这是痴人说梦
That's obviously not gonna happen.
看来你也是快人快语
I guess you've never heard of a sugarcoat either.
我想到了  我们必须要分手
I've got it... We have to break up.
-喔  分手  -我们不是真分手
-Whoa. Break up? -We don't need to break up for real.
我们假分手
We'll fake break up,
球队就会认为扫把星没了
The team will think the jinx is gone,
他们就会轻松很多  你们就能赢球了
They'll relax, you guys can win again.
主意不错
That could work.
好吧  那我们之间发生了什么
Okay, so what's our story?
-我们为什么分手呢  -我偷腥了
-Why are we breaking up? -I met someone else.
-好吧  是谁  -塞奇·勒福尔
-Okay, but who? -Serge Lefleur.
-谁  -塞奇是
-Excuse me? -Serge was.
我八岁时候的意淫男友
My imaginary boyfriend when I was eight.
他  他戴着丝绒贝雷帽
He... he had a velvet beret.
骑着独轮车
And rode a unicycle.
原来你的意淫男友是个小丑
So your imaginary boyfriend was a mime.
没错  一个可以上篮的小丑
Yeah, a mime who could make a layup.
嘿
Hey!
你绝对不会相信的
You won't believe this...
老爸老妈要把我送到军事学校
Mom and dad are sending me to military school.
噢  太悲剧了
Oh, this is terrible!
这个嘛  悲剧的是你
Well, maybe for you,
对于我来说  我的活动空间翻倍了
But I just doubled my living space.
你怎么能这么说
How can you say that?
怎么了  我算错数了吗
What, did I get the math wrong?
我的意思是  我知道我到处惹是生非
I mean, I know I've been bad,
但他们也不至于把我送走吧
But how can they just send me away?
你必须要体谅下老爸老妈
Well, you gotta hand it to mom and dad...
当家里又添新丁的时候
When you're adding a new kid,
就想抛弃一个老丁
You kinda wanna get rid of an old one.
怎么不抛弃你  你不是快上大学了吗
What about you? You'll be leaving for college soon.
盖比  地球人都知道我哪也去不了
Gabe, everyone knows I'm not going anywhere.
对吧  查莉
Right, Charlie?
-那还用说  -嗯
-True dat. -<i>Mmm.</i>
他们准备把我送到一个叫做格雷斯顿学院的地方
They're sending me to some place called Graystone academy.
格雷斯顿学院
Graystone academy.
啊  找到了  “格雷斯顿学院
Ah, found it. "Graystone academy:
折磨小男孩  始于一八七三年”
Breaking boys' spirits since 1873."
好吧  肯定有什么办法能逃过此劫
Okay, there... there has gotta be some way out of this.
说实话  我不太善于思考
Well, I'm not very good at thinking of things.
好吧  继续说
Okay, go on.
说不了了  我说过我不善于思考
No, that's it. I'm not very good at thinking of things.
我想到了
I've got it.
我只要表现的乖点
I'll just start behaving better.
如果让老爸老妈知道我有多乖后
If I show mom and dad how good I can be,
他们就不会送我走了
Then they'll never send me away.
有个问题  你的计划是变成乖乖仔
Just one problem, your plan requires you to be good.
你有过当乖乖仔的经验吗
You have no experience in that.
不用担心  我会去学的  如果我不学
Well, I'm gonna have to learn. It's either that.
-我就只能去军事学校了  -拜拜  盖比
-Or I'm off to military school. -Bye-bye, Gabe.
嘿  你昨晚做的什么梦
Hey, what were you dreaming last night?
-你怎么老是踢我  -我梦到你在打呼噜
-You kept kicking me. -I dreamt you were snoring.
噢  早上好
Oh, good morning.
两位吗
Table for two?
-搞什么  -你给我们做早点了
-What's all this? -You made us breakfast?
不光是早点  皇阿玛
Not just any breakfast, dad.
还有三个鸡蛋  煎饼
Three eggs filled with pancakes,
培根  冷披萨
Bacon and cold pizza.
你给我做了满汉全席
You made me a boblette?
当然  额娘  我为您准备了营养早餐
And, mom, a healthy breakfast for you...
有燕麦粥和新鲜的水果
Oatmeal and fresh fruits.
成了  老实交代你又捅了什么娄子  惹祸精
Okay, I wanna know what you did right now, mister.
我没捅什么篓子
I didn't do anything.
我只是发觉到你们是多么伟大的父母啊
I just realized what great parents I have.
这次满汉全席吃得真爽
This is the best boblette I've ever had.
盖比  说真的  我想知道
Gabe, seriously, I wanna know...
在这个季节  你是在哪弄到的蓝莓啊
Where you got blueberries, 'cause they're not even in season.
一会我回来洗碗
I'll be back later to do the dishes.
噢  对了  皇阿玛
Oh and, dad,
我给你备好了午餐
I made you lunch.
我还是觉得他另有所图
I still think he's up to something.
噢  我滴乖乖  他给我做了私房三明治
Oh, dear lord, he made me a bob-wich.
泰迪  我们要谈谈  现在
Teddy, we have to talk right now.
-谈什么  -关于你背着我偷腥
-About what? -About you cheating on me.
什么  我没有
Well, I don't actu...
难道非要现在谈吗
Do we have to do this here,
在众目睽睽之下
In front of everybody?!
你再重复遍台词
You were saying?
-我听说你背着我去偷腥  -噢
-I heard you're cheating on me. -Oh.
有人看见你和
Someone saw you with...
和萨基·勒夫卢
With Sarge Lefloo.
是塞奇·勒福尔吧
You mean serge lefleur?
那个英俊时尚的法国小伙
The handsome, dashing french boy.
却不在咱们学校上学
Who doesn't go to our school?
没错  就是他
Yeah, that guy.
噢  等一下
Oh, hold on.
哎呦  噢  好啊  我的小可爱  你好吗
Oops. <i>Oh, bonjour,</i> <i>mon petit chou-chou. Ca va?</i>
这下尴尬了
This is awkward.
-分手快乐  -你也是
-Good break-up. -You too.
-又见面了  -PJ  有事吗
-Hello, again. -P.J., what's up?
我今早注意到我的鬓角不是很匀称啊
I noticed this morning that my sideburns are a little uneven.
-是吗  -是啊
-They are? -Uh-huh.
好了  现在匀称了
There, now they're even.
好吧  但我的脑袋一般都歪着
Yeah, but this is kinda my natural head position.
感觉挺潇洒的
It makes me seem folksy.
好吧  坐下吧
Okay, have a seat.
成了  现在又潇洒又匀称
Done! Now you're folksy and even.
俺听说了  击下掌
Heard the news! Up top!
-听说什么了  -甩掉那个大帅哥
-What news? -You dropped him like he's hot,
-尽管他不帅  -噢
-even though he's not! -Oh.
艾薇  我们其实
Ivy, we're actually...
-我们没有  -俺不敢相信
-We're not really... -I couldn't believe.
你首先带回了那条狗
You got back with that dog in the first place.
斯宾塞和我还在一起
Spencer and I are still together.
能让俺说完吗
You didn't let me finish.
-俺喜欢小狗  -好吧
-I love dogs. -Yeah.
好了  听着  我们暂时先分手
Yeah, see, we staged the break-up.
当他们今晚赢下比赛之后
After they win the game tonight,
我们再告诉大家  我们没分手
We'll tell everyone we're still together.
然后他们就会知道我不是个扫把星了
And they'll know I was never a jinx.
-啊  -我听说了
-Ah. -Heard the news!
击掌庆祝
Up top!
-我们没分手  -能让我说完吗
-We're still together. -You didn't let me finish.
“之因为
"Just because.
爱  盖比留”
Love, Gabe."
他绝对捅了大娄子了
He must've done something really really bad.
最近有没有人看到过达布尼夫人
Has anyone seen Mrs. Dabney lately?
也许我们误解他了
Or maybe we're misreading this.
-此话怎讲  -亲爱的  也许盖比迈过了那道坎
-What do you mean? -Honey, maybe Gabe has finally turned that corner.
也许我们应该给予他
And maybe we should be giving him.
一些正面的鼓励
Some positive reinforcement.
好吧  如果他想痛改前非
Well, I guess if he's trying to be a good kid,
我们也可努力做位好家长
We could try to be good parents.
对我们来说都是挑战
New territory for all of us?
嘿  乖儿子
Hey, buddy.
跟我走  上车
Come on, get in the car.
上车  去哪
Get in the car? Why?
-我们去买冰淇淋  -不
-We're going for ice cream. -No!
不吃冰淇淋  你不能逼我
No ice cream! You can't make me!
好吧  呃  酸奶怎么样
Okay. Uh, yogurt?
我知道你们的阴谋
I know what's going on here.
我是不会中你们的圈套的
And I'm not going down like this!
-后退  我不走  -嘿  喔  喔  嘿  盖比
-Get back! I won't go! -Hey, whoa whoa! Hey, Gabe!
-你干嘛啊  -我不想去军事学校
-What are you doing? -I don't want to go to military school.
军事学校
Military school?
别不承认  我在厨房偷听到你俩的谈话了
Don't deny it! I overheard you two talking in the kitchen.
噢  你以为
Oh, you thought...
你以为今天就送你走吗
You think that you're leaving today.
你的启程日期还悬而未决
Your departure date is still being determined.
什么时候走全看你的表现了  对吧  老鲍
It all depends on how you behave, right, Bob?
对
Right.
我不想去格雷斯顿学院
I don't wanna go to Graystone academy.
我想在家磨练我的精神
I want my spirit to be broken at home.
被我深爱的人所磨练
By the people I love.
好吧  我试试打电话给柯林克
Well, I guess I could call Colonel...
上校
Klink...
告诉他我们会再三考虑的
And tell him that we might reconsider.
噢  谢谢
Oh, thank you.
-谢谢  -不用谢
-Thank you. -You're welcome.
现在
Now...
楼上的浴室可不会自己打扫的
There's a bathroom upstairs that's not gonna clean itself.
好的  我这就去  我这就去
Okay, I'm on it. I'm on it.
怎  怎  怎么回事
Wh-wha-what... What's going on?
-这是谁啊  -呃  四点半的预约啊
-Who is this? -Umm, my 4:30 appointment.
你先去洗头吧  我在这等你
Why don't you head back to the shampoo station and I'll be right there?
洗 洗头
Sh-shampoo?
我以为这是咱俩的专属
I thought that was our thing.
PJ  你又不是我的唯一顾客
P.J., you're not my only client.
噢  如今我成顾客了
Oh, so now I'm just a client?
你一直是顾客啊
You've always been just a client.
好吧  没有你我照样可以理发
Fine. Two can play this game.
杰里  请给我刮刮胡子
Jerry, gimme a shave, please.
没问题  孩子  坐下吧
Sure, kid. Have a seat.
-噢  嘿  小泰  -噢  好啊  艾薇
-Oh hey, T. -Oh hello, Ivy.
噢  我猜你已经听说了
Oh, I guess you've probably heard.
斯宾塞和我掰了
That Spencer and I broke up.
但是我的新男友有点忙
So my new boyfriend serge was busy,
所以我就前来支持下球队
And I decided I'd come and support the team.
你怎么这么说话
Why are you talking like that?
噢  艾薇  我平常就这么说话啊
Oh, Ivy, this is how I normally talk,
尤其当我不是扫把星的时候
Especially now that I'm not a jinx.
好吧  这场比赛会很难熬的
Yeah, this is gonna be a long game.
如果这球斯宾塞没投进  我们就输了
If Spencer misses this shot, we lose.
噢  噢  好耶
Oh! Oh yes!
好耶  好耶  好耶
Yes yes yes!
-呜  呜  -你干嘛呢
-Whoo-hoo! -What are you doing?
我要告诉全世界  我们没分手
I'm telling the whole world we're still together!
我们是不会分手的
We never broke up!
鉴于比赛胜利了  说明我不是个扫把星  哈
And since we won, I'm not a jinx! Ha!
-泰迪  -嗯
-Teddy. -Hmm?
现在是平局
The score is <i>tied.</i>
噢
<i>Oh.</i>
我错了
My bad.
我要投中这个罚球  才能赢
I have to make this foul shot to win.
好吧  没问题  继续加油
Okay. Yeah, carry on.
祝你好运  别有压力
Good luck. No pressure.
如果他投丢了  别说我认识你
If he misses this, I would not wanna be you.
好耶
Yes!
-可以了吗  -可以了
-Now? -Now.
-早上好  -噢  早上好
-Good morning. -Oh, good morning.
你表现得越来越好了
The presentation just keeps getting better and better.
好吧  今天吃什么
Well, what have we got on the menu today?
我希望是私房玉米煎饼
I'm hoping for a breakfast bob-urrito.
请上眼
All right.
看看
Voila.
什么都没有啊  怎么回事
There's nothing here. What's going on?
我告诉你怎么回事
I'll tell you what's going on.
我百度了下格雷斯顿学院
I did a little research on Graystone academy.
根本就没有柯林克上校这个人
There is no Colonel Klink.
那是因为队长柯克接替了他的位置
That's because he was replaced by Captain Kirk.
别逗了  你俩  你俩就是跟我闹着玩呢
Come on, guys. You were just messing with me.
你们是不会把我送去军事学校的
You were never gonna send me to military school.
是啊  不会的
No, we weren't,
但是我们可以
But we could.
不  你们不可以
No, you can't.
不管我捅多大的娄子
No matter how much trouble I get into,
你俩爱我爱的太深了
You guys love me too much.
我会爱你更深一点的
I'd love you a little more.
如果你给我弄个私房玉米煎饼
If you made me a breakfast bob-urrito.
还有一碗燕麦粥配上美味的蓝莓
And a bowl of oatmeal with those yummy blueberries.
好吧  马上来
All right, coming right up.
噢  不过首先
Oh, but first
我需要你们签了这个
I'm gonna need you guys to sign this.
好了  查莉  盖比逃过军事学校这一劫
Well, Charlie, Gabe's not going to militarschool,
我也摆脱了扫把星的恶名
And I'm no longer considered a jinx,
所以大家所有人都安然无恙
So everything's looking good here.
嘿  查莉
Hey, Charlie.
好吧  不是所有人
Well, almost everything.
怎么回事
What happened?
杰里  我的理发师  你说怎么回事
Jerry, my barber, is what happened.
-看起来好痛啊  -你应该再看看我的腿
-It looks painful. -You should see my legs.
鉴于他是你哥
And you're related to him,
所以祝你好运喽  查莉
So good luck, Charlie.
你去哪了  比赛都快结束了
Where have you been? The game's almost over.
约会去了
I was on a date.
噢  和谁啊
Oh, with who?
塞奇·勒福尔
Serge Lefleur.
你知道他只是想象出来的  对吧
You know he's imaginary, right?
呃  别听她瞎说  宝贝
Uh, don't listen to her, baby.
独轮车那件事  我是怎么跟你说的
What did I tell you about that unicycle?
外面骑去
Take it outside.
你来得正好  如果斯宾塞投进了
You got here just in time. If Spencer makes this shot,
我们将赢得州际冠军
We win the state championship.
噢
Oh!
休在我的地盘撒野
Not in my house.